{
    "subject": "resource/Pescanova",
    "predicate": "ontology/subsidiary",
    "object": "resource/Aliholding",
    "human_readable": "Pescanova is a subsidiary of Aliholding.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9359291791915894,
            "question": "Is Aliholding the parent company of Pescanova?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9151200652122498,
            "question": "What company is Pescanova a subsidiary of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9081754684448242,
            "question": "Does Aliholding control Pescanova?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8601318597793579,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Aliholding and Pescanova?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7918418049812317,
            "question": "Who owns Pescanova?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7273619174957275,
            "question": "To which company does Pescanova belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7012821435928345,
            "question": "Which company has ownership over Pescanova?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6490982174873352,
            "question": "Is Pescanova an independent company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5033360719680786,
            "question": "What is the higher-level entity that owns Pescanova?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47106051445007324,
            "question": "Name the parent company of Pescanova."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pescanova is a subsidiary of Aliholding.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8217_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the higher-level entity that owns Pescanova?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8217_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Pescanova an independent company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8217_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which company has ownership over Pescanova?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8217_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8217_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8217_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8217_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8217_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8217_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8217_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8217_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8217_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8217_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8217_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Pescanova is a subsidiary of Aliholding\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nReasoning:\nThe context information provides details about Pescanova, including its structure and activities. However, it does not mention anything about Aliholding being related to Pescanova in any way. In fact, the text mentions that Pescanova is a parent of Grupo Pescanova (a group which comprises a number of controlled entities with operations established worldwide), but there is no connection mentioned between Pescanova and Aliholding. Therefore, the triple \"Pescanova is a subsidiary of Aliholding\" cannot be supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provided do not mention any information about Pescanova being a subsidiary of Aliholding. Instead, the documents describe Pescanova as an independent company engaged in the fishing industry with various operations and subsidiaries of its own."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}